i have and always will fully support palestine and i just felt the need to put that out there
because a brand really tried to pay me to change my opinion today that's not going to happen you
cannot buy my morals i had a brand deal lined up with this particular brand i've even filmed the
video and everything today was the day i was meant to post it today i also posted on my instagram
loads of pictures from the palestine protest in london right i messaged them i'm like am i still
good to post the video at this time they said no then i received a essay basically saying that
they're not willing to work with me anymore because i publicly said that i support palestine
i was like that's fine because i as much don't want to work with you if you support innocent
people lying oh shit sorry i dashed my remote onto the floor and then i thought it was over it wasn't
i then received another message where they said if i take the post down and publicly announce that i
do not support that they will pay me basically double the amount that we agreed on and they
would repost my video onto their feed which obviously has fucking loads of followers i am so
in what actual right mind do you think that you can buy my morals they really wanted me to come
online and be like yeah i'm actually okay with these innocent people just these innocent children
as well just so you all know i support palestine if you want to unfollow me because of this that's
fine if other brands don't want to work with me because of this that's also okay there's quite
clearly bigger problems in the world we're discussing them right now